Previously on "Marvel's
Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D."...
What is that thing parading
around as Grant Ward?
He connects to the Inhumans,
and they instantly joined the hive.
I have to get back to the base.
They have something we need.
Daisy showed me the Kree
artifact you gave her,
and it's missing its companion piece.
I buried it. What is it?
The only thing that can destroy me.
How do we disinfect Daisy?
Meet Dr. Holden Radcliffe.
You're the only one that
can save my friend.
With your help, we're going
to redefine humanity.
H-how could you...
By re-creating the same
Kree experiment that was done to me.
It was in that moment
my world had changed forever.
The Kree Reapers brought
me back to their ship
and began the experiment.
I didn't know it then, but the Reapers
were using their own Kree
blood to transform my DNA.
Once they changed what I was,
the Reapers took the final step,
fulfilling the promise
of what I would become.
So that's how you became an Inhuman.
Myself and many others.
Put through the Kree
experiment thousands of years ago.
These first
Inhumans... they were your ancestors.
Your ancestors started Hydra.
You fought to bring me back,
yet are the only
faithful to evade being captured
after Gideon
Malick's spineless betrayal.
Well... the time has
come for your reward.
Thank you, but...
what does that have
to do with your story?
Isn't it obvious?
We've been working hard to
re-create the Kree experiment.
And you're next.
Any word on Daisy?
Nope.
You tried reaching
out to any old contacts?
- Uh-huh.
- Maybe if...
We're handling it.
I just want to help.
If I'm locked down on the base,
at least let me do something.
The last time you helped wasn't helpful.
Alisha had answers. I was
just trying to make her talk.
You threatened to torture her.
- How'd that work out?
- I'm not going to apologize
for trying to save someone I care about.
We all care about Daisy.
- Oh, it's not the same.
- No.
The rest of us have
known her a lot longer.
You really want to help?
Stop trying.
This is hopeless.
Just hold on, Simmons.
The antitoxin appears to be
fighting the Hive parasites.
Yes, but first,
it would probably
destroy the host's immune system,
and who even knows how it
will react with Inhuman DNA?
Well, I'll admit that it's not ideal,
but what other choice do we have?
You didn't see Daisy.
She acted like we were
still best of pals,
all while threatening to murder me.
No, you're right. I didn't see that.
I was much too busy listening
to the disgusting face of Grant
Ward act like my dead boyfriend.
That's true. That does sound worse.
Right. If this was a
competition, I would win.
I had to shoot him three
times just to shut him up.
- Bet that felt good.
- Yeah, it did,
though it would have felt
better had he actually died,
instead of just sort of oozing.
What if Hive can't be killed?
What then?
This antitoxin might
be the best chance we have
to free Daisy of his hold on her.
Yes, or it could put her into
cardiac arrest or seizures.
Okay, but, then, we
find a way to test it.
And who's going to volunteer for that?
We need an Inhuman, and
those who aren't in hiding
are already under Hive's
sway and would kill us for trying.
I'll do it.
You can test it out on me.
Footage is from some
mechanic's garage in south Wyoming.
What's in south Wyoming?
Not much, by the looks of it.
Says it was an old mining town
that went through a natural-gas boom.
But with the influx of dirty wells,
it drove out almost all the locals.
And the ones that remained
were recently bought
out by a shell corporation.
- Owned by Malick.
- Yeah.
And now the town's
crawling with military.
It seems the personal guard
that we encountered in
Malick's hidden bunker...
They got out with Hive, relocated.
Won't be easy to grab Daisy.
You realize this is a trap, right?
Why?
W-W... Because we have a lead?
Because Daisy's a highly trained spy.
No S.H.I.E.L.D. agent would
get caught on camera that easily.
She's trying to draw us out.
Daisy warned Fitz not to
have S.H.I.E.L.D. follow.
Why would she want to lure us in now?
It doesn't add up.
None of this adds up.
There's an ancient Inhuman
controlling one of my best agents,
the same agent who helped reprogram
the facial-recognition software
that she just got flagged on.
What?
Suddenly, Daisy doesn't
know how it works?
Ohh, no, I don't... I
don't...  it's...
I th...
I think she wants us to rescue her.
- Mack.
- Look, just hear me out.
Daisy's too strong to give
up control without a fight.
I think there's a part of
her that's still resisting Hive.
That's just not the
reality. It's you projecting.
Look, Fitz said Daisy wasn't a zombie.
She's still herself, only
with Hive's agenda.
That means she's still in there.
I wish that was true, Mack, believe me,
but we cannot be driven
by our emotions on this.
That's how Ward ended up dead, which
is how we ended up in this mess.
Sir...
We don't have time to debate this.
You and I need to get on the same page.
Understood.
Good.
'Cause I'm sending a team in there,
and I want you and May to lead it.
So, then, we are saving Daisy.
This isn't a rescue
mission, Agent Mackenzie...
it's a targeted strike.
We're gonna kill Hive.
This town represents
the worst of humanity...
allowing the greed of a few
to destroy the needs of many.
Their water was
poisoned, which drove them out.
The great failing was their unwillingness
to band together.
Sometimes it's hard to join forces.
You need a good leader.
Like Coulson?
He was the reason
why I joined S.H.I.E.L.D.
S.H.I.E.L.D. is no
better than those Kree Reapers,
both making soldiers for
their never-ending wars.
My friends at
S.H.I.E.L.D. wanted to stop wars,
not start them.
By building giant
battleships floating in the sky?
The only reason
S.H.I.E.L.D. exists is to fight wars.
But isn't that why we exist?
I mean, that's what the Kree Reapers
were hoping to make, right?
Soldiers.
Which is not what I became.
Sometimes, the world's
greatest miracles happen by accident.
The world I was born into was primitive.
It has evolved at a
remarkable pace while I was away.
So, what happened back then, to
get you kicked off of Earth?
People saw the connection
I had with other Inhumans,
and that made them afraid.
That fear bred
paranoia, which led to civil war.
Not much has changed, really.
Only now we have the ability
to re-create the Kree experiment.
Are the patients ready, Dr. Radcliffe?
Yes... not that you did us any favors
with your alien-abduction story.
Took a good hour to assure them
there'd be no probes of any sort.
Well, your method is much more elegant.
Not to mention more efficient,
now that I've added
the Terrigen Crystals
- to the prokaryotic compound.
- W...
You can change their
DNA and turn them Inhuman,
all at the same time?
Ah, the old one-two punch.
That particular bit of
ingenuity was my idea.
So... to the moment at hand.
The world fears our kind of power
because not everyone has it.
Only billionaires can build iron suits.
Only the military can
make super soldiers,
which can only lead to a war of its own,
whereas I plan to apply a
more, uh, collectivist philosophy.
Does, uh, does that
mean we can get started?
Yes.
Right. Great.
Oh, God, please, make it stop!
How many others we got?
Four volunteers from operations...
aware of the danger and
all pretty gung ho.
Don't know if that'll be
enough to take out Hive.
Maybe not.
But lucky for us,
Coulson had Fitz open up the Cupboard.
Whoa! I got dibs on that.
Oh, sorry, O'Brien.
Coulson promised it
to me when I signed up.
It's in my contract.
Eyes up front, everyone.
Hive is unlike
anything we've ever faced,
which is why each of
you will be outfitted
with the best S.H.I.E.L.D.
has to offer...
full Kevlar Tac, heat-sensitive infrared,
and enough Splinter Bombs
to turn a small army into pixie dust.
The rest of the gear is up for grabs.
What's the Calvary packing?
- If I need a gun, I'll take one.
- No.
You'll be taking this one.
We can't leave anything to chance.
You seem extra motivated.
Daisy was my partner. This is on me.
Why is everyone making
this about themselves?
Because I should have seen it, May,
but between her Inhuman love connection
and me licking my wounds after
Bobbi and Hunter left,
I took my eyes off the ball.
A good partner would've
seen that she was turned.
None of us saw it.
And you need to get your head straight.
This mission isn't about Daisy.
Agreed.
It's about me making things right.
Wouldn't you have to be
infected with Hive's parasites
to test the antitoxin?
Not necessarily.
Simmons gives me the drug
first, takes my tissue sample,
then infects that with Hive's parasites.
This antitoxin will
destroy your immune system.
It could kill you.
You're not the only doctor here.
From what I can tell, the risks
aren't as high as what you're saying.
Don't pretend that's
really your medical opinion.
I'm not pretending... you're
being overly cautious.
Yeah, and you're being a lovesick fool
trying to make a grand gesture.
Fitz... any thoughts?
Uh...
I agree with Simmons that
the antitoxin could be dangerous...
but I also think there's
a chance it could work.
If Lincoln dies, do you
really want to be responsible?
No, of course I don't, but
this could save Daisy.
Daisy would never want
someone acting so recklessly
to save her.
Well, then, I'm glad it's not up to her.
I'm sorry, Agent Campbell.
Come on. Y-You got to reconsider.
My decision's final.
Fitz-Simmons, start
looking at other options.
We'll go from there.
Ohh!
One Martian Multi-ball,
three Bumper Blasters,
and a 3-Way Rocket Combo.
Boom!
Good luck beating that score.
Better keep your hat on, Dundee,
'cause somebody don't
play when it comes to pinball.
Mmm. Ah!
This beer is bloody wonderful.
I thought Aussies hated American beer.
Only when we got to pay for it.
It is good to be back in
the real world again.
Yeah, what made you go all Ted Kaczynski
in that trailer, anyway?
Don't know, really.
Just never found
people to be my cup of tea.
They didn't like me.
I didn't like them, so I
thought I'd do everyone a favor
and move as far
away as humanly possible.
That sounds pretty lonely.
Yeah.
Never really figured on that part.
Aww.
You're a little baby bird,
all fixed up and back in the wild.
I'm not keen on infantilizing,
but I would be willing to let
it slide for a proper dance.
Oh.
Oh! Whoo!
Okay.
Let's don't get your
rhinestones in a bunch, cowboy.
Let's just keep it to pinball.
Please tell me you're not pining
over Stinkin' Lincoln.
You know, James, just because you
don't care about anyone else
doesn't mean the rest of us don't.
Sorry. I didn't mean to offend.
It's just... you were S.H.I.E.L.D.
So those people you care
about are the same ones
that are trying to
stop what we're doing here.
It's not their fault.
They don't know any better.
Doesn't matter if they
know any better or not...
they're on the opposite side.
I can't see any way it
doesn't end badly for them.
There might be one way.
Oh, yeah?
And what's that?
We make them understand.
The genetic makeup of
Inhumans is incredibly complex.
We were bound to run into complications.
You assured me this would work.
Yes, and it would have
i-if I'd been provided with
the right ingredients.
Are you implying the mistake was mine?
No.
No, no.
Well, yes, but it
wasn't an intentional mistake.
You see, the thing is, I
need DNA from a living Kree
to complete the genome sequence.
The DNA you gave me... your blood...
it's from a... dead host...
a handsome but dead host.
It's no good.
I mean, it's great for you,
but it... for this, it's no good.
If this were true, why are
you just telling me this now?
Ohh, I wasn't sure.
I was swept up in the moment!
I wanted to change the world!
And besides, you're very frightening.
Well, you are right to be scared.
I don't need you.
I can just kill you and
inhabit your body,
take your mind, your memories.
Yeah, that's a really bad idea.
You should ask my therapist.
My childhood was a total mess.
The swim team were not nice to me.
Plus, I can make this work.
Why should I believe you?
Because I want it to work.
This is game-changing stuff...
kick-starting mankind into a new gear.
Everything I've
done leading up to this...
it just pales.
I promise, you won't regret this.
I'm your guy.
Yeah, I've been meaning to...
been meaning to ask about those.
What are they for, exactly?
If you were scared before...
you should be terrified now.
Our intelligence suggests
there's at least 40
enemy combatants on the ground.
And what about Hive?
We've still yet to
verify his location, sir.
Okay.
The plan's simple... go
in, kill Hive, get out.
What's protocol when it comes
to the other Inhumans in town?
Do not engage unless
absolutely necessary.
These people are under Hive's control.
We don't want to hurt them.
I can't be with you on the ground,
but I will be
watching your helmet feeds.
Be careful and be smart.
This may be our only
chance to catch Hive by surprise.
And worst-case scenario,
if Hive can't be killed?
I suggest running... very fast... away.
Jemma...
are we good after, you
know, our disagreement?
Oh, yeah, of course we're good.
If I wanted a boyfriend who agreed
with everything I said,
I never would have
broken up with Milton.
Ugh...
Milton!
He was the absolute worst,
what with his stupid, fat
cabbage head of his.
"Hi. I'm... Hi. I'm Milton."
More like a Brussels sprout, really.
But Milton's odd-shaped head aside,
we should make a point to
never let work disagreements
affect our relationship outside of work.
Couldn't agree more,
Simmons, especially since we both know
who tends to be right most of the time.
Oh, I assume you're referring to the one
who finished top of our
class at S.H.I.E.L.D. Academy.
Now, that is a sore
point, because we both know
that if I'd just stayed
up and studied all night...
Lincoln.
I'm tired of arguing.
Lincoln, no!
Lincoln. Hey. Lincoln.
Look at me. Look at me!
I just want to help.
This is an elixir,
and it will hopefully
counter the antitoxin.
N-No.
It's gonna work.
We don't have time for
this. Your body is shutting down.
I can handle it.
Please... just let me do this.
You got eyes on this, Coulson?
Affirmative.
There's no sign of Hive anywhere.
We don't have time to
search the entire town.
Isn't that the Inhuman Hive
picked up in South Dakota?
Yeah, he's a real blowhard.
That might work.
Hey, this area's authorized
for Hydra personnel only.
Who the hell are you?
Hello, gorgeous.
I'm James.
Single, 33, originally from Brisbane.
I'm a Leo, with a little dab of Scorpio
thrown in there for good measure.
I like a decent drink, a decent meal,
and an indecent lass,
and not necessarily in that order.
And you are...?
Nauseous...
Mm.
And wondering what you're doing here.
Uh, you're definitely not Hydra.
Mnh-mnh.
This means they brought in
other contractors since Malick died?
Ah!
A contractor? Really?
Is that what I look like to you?
Listen, big shot, this isn't a game.
I need you to tell me
what you're doing here.
I'd rather show than tell.
Y-Y-You're... You're one of them.
That's right.
Kind of hand-picked by
the big man himself.
Kind of a number-one draft
pick, if you will.
I had no idea. Please,
you have to forgive me.
Have a drink with me, and
I might consider it.
You're not too bad for security.
Little icy.
Lucky for me, I don't get frostbite.
Were you like this before
you got your powers?
What... 101% awesome?
You bet.
Becoming Inhuman doesn't
change your personality.
Who knows?
Might even see for yourself one day.
Uh, the big man... he's
working on this experiment
turning humans into Inhumans, huh?
Ask nicely...
might even help you to
the front of the line.
That must be why
Hive grabbed Radcliffe...
to make his army.
Stay on alert.
You hear what Coulson just said?
Yeah, sorry.
I was just wondering
if there was a chance
this guy doesn't get his ass whupped.
Not a chance.
Alisha said you wanted to see me.
You and I share similar paths.
We were both created by outside forces.
I'm not sure I'm following.
My powers were given by the Kree...
yours by S.H.I.E.L.D.
They're the ones who made us.
Why are you worried about S.H.I.E.L.D.?
Because I'm curious if you
can defeat what made you.
The people at
S.H.I.E.L.D. are my friends.
Friends who will turn on you,
who will try and
sabotage the connection we share.
Only because they don't understand,
but they will if we can make
them share our connection.
You want to put your
friends through the Kree experiment.
Once Radcliffe has worked
out the kinks, yeah.
Yeah, I do.
They may not be receptive to that idea.
Well, I have to at least try.
It's the only way we can save them.
And what if you fail,
if they decide to turn on you instead,
to come after us
with their weapons of war,
to kill me, to kill all of us?
What then?
Then I would rip their hearts out.
Hearing that comes as a relief,
especially now that
our plans have changed.
I'm sorry.
There was just no other choice.
We both thought it was
the right thing to do.
Hey.
Don't act as if we're
on the same side on this.
Coulson gave you a direct
order, and you disobeyed.
Now... half the lab's
computers are fried,
not to mention the blown servers.
I'm sorry about that. Really, I am.
But the antitoxin is gonna work.
I can feel it.
Well, we won't know until Simmons
has run some more tests.
And for that, I'll need to
drill inside your head.
Wait.
The tissue sample you
need is from my brain?
That's correct... something
you would have known,
had you asked questions
instead of going behind our backs.
He's all yours, Doctor.
He sounds pretty amazing.
Oh, yeah.
He's got this whole Ziggy Stardust
vibe thing happening.
It's... It's quite epic.
Well, I would love to meet him.
Well, I just might be able to
broker an introduction for you.
Right now?
You'd really do that for me?
Not so sure if right now works.
I mean, he's kind of a busy guy, with
changing the world and everything.
Right.
No, no, no. Don't go
rainy-day blues on me.
He might still be in that
abandoned mining facility.
You got that?
On our way!
Why take over a town
and then move to the outskirts?
I don't know, but the
reason's probably not good.
Remember, this is Hive.
Be prepared to go in hot. Safeties off.
They were never on, sir.
I was hoping to spare you this,
but it was the only way.
They're coming for us.
You hearing this?
Sounds like some kind of radio.
What?
That's definitely no
radio I've ever seen.
I've seen that writing before.
Sir.
Get everyone out of there now!
You heard him! Move out! Go! Go!
- Move it!
- Who's coming?
S.H.I.E.L.D.?
Not the ones who made you...
the ones who made me.
Move! Go, go, go!
What the hell was that?
The Kree.
The Kree are here?
How did they even find us?
I sent them a signal.
The artifacts from James' trailer.
Are a failsafe to be used
if the Inhuman
experiment ever got out of control.
In case of emergency,
call Kree headquarters.
These Kree are not
from their home world.
They're Reapers.
They exist only to hunt.
And to find humans for your makers.
For thousands of years, they've
remained in stasis,
orbiting our solar system.
So they're coming here to do what...
clean up their mess?
These are the only
things that can defeat you.
Those are your exact words.
The Reapers are my greatest fear,
but with your help, I believe we will...
rip out their hearts.
Those words are yours.
That's really not what I meant.
I fought a Kree before.
They won't be easy to kill.
These Reapers are even deadlier,
which will make your
task more difficult.
My task?
For this experiment to work,
we need blood from a living Kree.
And I want you to get it.
Was that a spaceship?
It's too small... looks
like more of a satellite.
Why am I not relieved?
You find anything?
Just debris everywhere and
some really big footprints.
Like alien footprints, right?
That's what we're talking about here?
Great.
Now we have more
players to contend with.
The frickin' aliens just landed.
We're not... We're not gonna take
a moment and let that soak in?
Well, the question is,
whose side are they on?
Dude, run! Go!
Inhuman.
Actually, that's Inhumans, plural.
No!
You should be proud
of what we've become.
He's taking out Hydra agents.
Or everything he comes across.
This will be a lot easier
if that guy's on our side.
Why would Hive signal these things?
Maybe he's hoping to form
some sort of creepy dude alliance.
These things are hunters, not allies.
Coulson, what are our orders?
Follow at a close distance,
but stay out of that
thing's cross hairs.
It senses something in that church.
Yeah, my money's on Hive.
Daisy.
Those aren't our orders.
- Mack.
- I got to try.
I'll meet you at the extraction point.
That wasn't me.
Inhuman filth.
You said you were going
to handle this thing.
- Now we are both gonna die!
- Nobody's dying here today.
What was that last sound?
The spine.
Now drain it.
I've spent a thousand
years wondering what would happen
should the blue angels ever return.
You're smaller than I remember.
Now's our chance to go in and unload
while Papa Smurf's got him distracted.
Stand down.
The Kree might just do the job for us.
We don't have to fight.
I'm still grateful to you for making me.
We should not have chosen you.
That was providence guiding your hand.
Then what guides my hand now?
Poor guy.
He doesn't have much longer.
Will there be enough blood
for the experiment to work?
Yeah, absolutely. I
mean, you were fantastic.
We should have all we
need in the next hour.
In fact, I'm happy to take it from here.
I-I-If you've got somewhere
else you need to be,
then feel free to...
She's coming with me.
I told Fitz to stay away.
No can do...
not when my partner needs help.
I don't need your help.
There's plenty of
evidence here to the contrary.
You don't understand.
I'm doing this to help you.
And now is murdering a
blue alien gonna help me?
It's the only way to save you.
We're gonna make you into an Inhuman.
This isn't you.
I know this is hard for
you to hear, but this is me.
I'm not lost anymore.
Everyone at S.H.I.E.L.D. can finally
stop trying to save me.
- This is different.
- Is it?
I mean, first, S.H.I.E.L.D. rescues
me from the Rising Tide,
and then from my
admittedly not-so-great parents,
and now, once again,
S.H.I.E.L.D.'s rallied the
troops to save poor Daisy.
Because you're sick.
That... thing is a parasite.
It's messing with your head.
That's what S.H.I.E.L.D.'s been doing.
Look at us, Mack!
You were a mechanic, I was a hacker,
and now, s-somehow, we're soldiers?
The world's changing. We had to adapt.
We had no choice.
S.H.I.E.L.D. made us
into what it needed.
No.
Nobody at
S.H.I.E.L.D. made you do anything.
But Coulson knew I was lost,
so he'd offered up his
team of misfit toys
just to fill that emptiness.
That team cares about you.
I care about you.
So what's that make us... friends?
Friends. Partners.
Bobbi was your partner once.
How'd that work out for you?
You know damn well Bobbi and
Hunter left S.H.I.E.L.D.
to protect us.
They left S.H.I.E.L.D.
because there was no reason to stay,
because nobody else at S.H.I.E.L.D.
mattered to them.
It wasn't hard to leave.
But I think you should
leave here, right now.
Part of you wants to come back.
That's how we found you.
What are you talking about?
Three hours ago,
we received security
footage of you outside this garage.
It sent a red flag up our system,
the same system you helped create.
So what... you think
that I meant for this to happen?
It wasn't an accident.
Something inside you is resisting.
I slipped up because I
wasn't thinking like a spy anymore,
because I don't need to be a
S.H.I.E.L.D. agent anymore.
- Tremors...
- No, no, Mack.
I cared about you, too.
After what happened with my parents,
I needed someone, and you...
you were almost
like a big brother to me.
But let's be honest...
you struggle to be a real brother
to the one that you have.
Leave Ruben out of this.
I understand how you're feeling.
But you don't need to
feel alone anymore.
We can fix it.
Now, what you're
feeling... it's not real.
What we feel is reality.
It's the way the world was meant to be.
Not my world.
I really wanted to save you, Mack.
Yeah.
Me, too.
If I can't save you, I guess
I'll save everyone else.
I'm no longer the scared
hunter you took all those years ago.
You should have stayed away!
Wait!
Please.
I'm not gonna fight you.
I wanted you to be a part of this.
Big Blue might just have this one.
Don't be so sure.
Sounds like Hive's nursing
a thousand-year grudge.
You made something great...
something divine...
and now you want to destroy it.
You are a failed experiment.
Sometimes, the world's
greatest miracles happen by accident.
Take the shot... now! Repeat!
Take the shot!
Piper!
We have to go! Now!
Now!
We could have had a
connection that was real.
Daisy, look at yourself.
You don't have to do this.
I need emergency evac now!
We got to get out of
here! Hurry up! He's coming!
He's coming!
I can't believe Daisy did this.
You were right about her.
Really wish I wasn't.
So...
Hive wants to turn any
human into an Inhuman,
regardless of that
person's existing genetic markers.
Might have succeeded,
had Mack not Splinter Bombed that Kree.
Well, does it even matter?
That thing... there's
nothing that can stop it.
Wait.
What happened?
Is Daisy okay?
The mission failed.
Daisy is still alive,
but they weren't able to stop Hive.
W-When did this happen?
They returned an hour ago.
An hour ago?
And you just...
kept me down here this whole time?
Well, you needed to rest.
I needed to be up there, helping,
not locked down here like some prisoner!
Your immune system is
completely shut down!
Anyone so much as
sneezes, and it might kill you.
So until you've fully recovered,
you are a
prisoner... you're my prisoner.
I'm sorry.
I-I just don't know what to do.
None of us do.
Did you at least tell
Coulson we might have a cure?
No.
Why not?
Because we don't.
That's what I came down to tell you...
the antitoxin...
it didn't work.
Now get some rest.
I ripped out its heart...
as discussed.
But you failed us.
I tried to stop him.
Then your efforts were lacking.
Not only did your
friend destroy everything
we've been working
towards, he also got away.
We put too much trust in you.
Your ties to S.H.I.E.L.D. are
stronger than you admit.
Leaves me with questions.
No.
You were right to trust me.
I'm finished with S.H.I.E.L.D.
And actually, I have answers.
The DNA you need... I have it.
Inhuman DNA is not enough.
We needed to drain actual Kree blood.
Which is what I have pumping
through my veins.
Coulson used it to bring
me back after Quinn shot me.
Ward should remember.
He does.
So, if you want this
experiment to work...
drain me.
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans